{
    "subject": "resource/RuPaul",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Drag_queen",
    "human_readable": "RuPaul is a Drag queen.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8093717694282532,
            "question": "Are there any other famous drag queens besides RuPaul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5315528512001038,
            "question": "What is RuPaul known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47009339928627014,
            "question": "What kind of performer is RuPaul?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4498266279697418,
            "question": "What shows is RuPaul associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37034872174263,
            "question": "Is RuPaul a male or female entertainer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3602561354637146,
            "question": "What does the term 'drag queen' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2088152915239334,
            "question": "Has RuPaul won any awards for their work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18804533779621124,
            "question": "What impact has RuPaul had on popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11567121744155884,
            "question": "What is the significance of RuPaul's career in the LGBTQ+ community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08577409386634827,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of drag performances?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=RuPaul is a Drag queen.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7655_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of RuPaul's career in the LGBTQ+ community?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7655_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact has RuPaul had on popular culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7655_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has RuPaul won any awards for their work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7655_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_164.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7655_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}